<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Here is the intro.xml file to be include inside book.xml -->
<!-- Note the word 'chapter' after DOCTYPE below.-->
<!DOCTYPE chapter PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.5//EN" 
    "http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.5/docbookx.dtd">
    
<chapter id="introduction">

<title>Introduction</title>

<sect1 id="products-used">
    <title>Products used in this software</title>
    
    <para>
    As many actual software, this software relies in many 
    external libraries to do its job. This isn't a novelty. 
    However, I want to specify this list just in case 
    everybody knows it. 
    </para>
    
<table frame='topbot'>
  <title>Softtware used</title>
  <tgroup cols='2' colsep='3' rowsep='1'>
    <thead>
    <row>
    <entry>Product</entry><entry>License / What it does</entry>
    </row>
    </thead>
    <tbody>
    <row>
      <entry>MantisConnect</entry>
      <entry>
      Propietary. It costs 50 euros if you plan
      to use this software for business (what else
      you would want this software for, mm??) 
      </entry>
    </row>
    <row>
      <entry>Spring</entry>
      <entry></entry>
    </row>
    <row>
      <entry></entry>
      <entry></entry>
    </row>
    </tbody>
  </tgroup>
</table>
    
</sect1>

<sect1 id="conventions">
    <title>Conventions used in this document</title>

    <para>
    We will start with the usual, how we write certain things 
    in the document: program listings, admonitions, and stuff like 
    that.
    </para>

    <caution>
    <title>This will be for special advices</title>
    <para>
    This box will be used when referring to 
    things that, when unproperly done, may damage 
    the correct behaviour of the program.
    </para>
    </caution>

    <warning>
    <title>This will be for warnings</title>
    <para>
    We will use this box to refer to things that you 
    have to put special care when doing them.
    </para>
    </warning>
    
    <tip>
    <title>This will be for advices and tricks</title>
    <para>
    We will use this box to refer to things that must 
    help in the configuration. 
    </para>
    </tip>
    
    <para>
    In general, filenames along this book will appear 
    with this type of text: <filename>this-is-a-filename.txt</filename>.
    Moreover, when refering to text that appear as an output
    of the computer (like the output of a log file), they will 
    appear as this:
    </para>
    
    <para>
    <screen>
2012-52-25 00:52:57 INFO  supermanhamuerto.nestor.MailReader       - Opening session...
2012-52-25 00:52:57 INFO  supermanhamuerto.nestor.MailReader       - url:http://localhost/mantisbt-1.2.8/api/soap/mantisconnect.php
    </screen>
    </para>
    
    <para>
    On the other hand, when speaking of things that must 
    be typed, the text will appear as this: <userinput>dir</userinput>.
    If the computer outputs the text, it will be shown 
    as this: <computeroutput>Hello world!!</computeroutput>
    </para>
    
    <sect2>
    <title>Linux or Windows??</title>
    
    <para>
    Whenever possible, I'll avoid to give the same instructions 
    for Windows&trade; and Linux, specially if they are more or 
    less the same. This will make the text more readable. This 
    document is highly technical and the audience is accustomed 
    to <quote>Linuxize</quote> the windows commands or to 
    <quote>Windize</quote> the linux ones.
    </para>
    
    </sect2>
    
</sect1>


</chapter>
